Previously on Sterling Point…
- Hello?
- Who are you?
What the fuck are you doing
in my grandfather's cottage?
I thought that this was my cottage.
You can sleep on the couch.
but you have to be gone in the morning.
- Connor?
- How's Canada?
Our mom. our adoptive mom.
I think she had
a secret biological daughter.
I didn't know you were comin' up.
You think I'd just dip forever?
Shit. shit. Fuck!
Oh. fuck.
Being here is making me realize
how little I think about my mom.
You're thinking about her now.
How do you know Annie?
We hung out with her all Canada Day.
I did not rent the cottage to her.
I don't know who the fuck this girl is.
- Hey.
- Ramona. slow down!
I'd like you to explain
why you broke into my cottage
and stole a photo of my dead mother.
'Cause she's my mother too!
- Did you know about me?
- No.
Great. So everyone's been
lying to us our whole life.
You said you were adopted?
So we're not related.
You're not my sister.
My mom had one daughter. and that was me.
But. Ramona. you didn't know her either.
- Do you think I should just leave?
- Did you get the answers you wanted?
I've barely scratched the surface.
Maybe that's your answer.
Are you coming or not?
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
- Oh. sorry. Thought you… I'm sorry.
- Oh!
- Sorry. you got your hands full. Um…
- Yeah.
How'd you sleep?
Uh. didn't. really.
Oh. sorry. That's a shame.
I heard you hammering outside.
Yeah. I'm just winterizing
so I can live here year-round.
Oh. Nice. Did you guys live
somewhere else the rest of the year?
This place called Barrie.
It's a few hours from here.
Nice. nice. What's the vibe in Barrie?
- There's no vibe. really. in Barrie.
- Mmm.
- Do you want some coffee? I made some.
- I'd love that.
Thanks.
And thank you for letting me stay here.
It was like…
It's really. really generous of you.
If there's anything I can do at all
to help out. or…
- Yeah.
- …do anything nice for you.
- I would really love to.
- You really don't…
- Thank you so much.
- Okay.
So. you're gonna live here year-round?
- That's the plan. Yeah.
- Awesome.
Just… Yeah.
Haven't been here in a while.
so everything's. like.
reminding me of Gordon. and…
just wanna get rid of all this furniture.
I can't look at it anymore.
Yeah.
Yeah. I'm sorry.
I bet that's really difficult.
Must be intense
to be around all of this stuff.
Is there anything I can do to help you.
or. like…
um. get some stuff out of here
or anything?
Uh… do you know how to use
a caulking gun?
I'm not actually comfortable
with firearms.
Oh. Sorry. I'm kidding.
- Oh.
- I don't know what that is. though. Sorry.
Yeah. it's okay. Um…
You can take that box of shit
Gord's been hoarding since the 1800s
- to the thrift store if you want.
- I can do that.
- All right.
- I can do that. Um…
Is… Is this Mom's stuff?
I'm not sure.
That is so cool.
Wow.
Oh. yeah. This is definitely Mom's stuff.
Look at this.
It's so pretty.
Aw! Collie lamp. That's really cute.
Did Mom have a collie?
Uh. no. Uh-uh.
I don't know
if we can throw this stuff away.
Yes. we can. It's trash.
Just. Gordon never wanted
to throw anything away.
Who's Jann Arden?
Cool.
Oh. my God. Look.
I wonder who she was making this for.
- Okay.
- Mixtape.
I told you.
I don't wanna keep any of this stuff.
Take it to the thrift store.
Cool. yeah. Of course.
- Um. where is the thrift store?
- On the mainland.
Okay. cool. Cool. Thanks.
- Everything run all right for ya?
- Eh…
You know. the cup holders
were a little sticky.
Do you guys not wash the boats
in between renters?
- Uh. no. We do.
- Oh.
Just not well. I guess.
Sorry about that.
What're you gonna do?
All right. so your total for today
comes up to…
um… $425.
We're cash only.
How much. again?
$425.
- Have a nice day.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
- Ramona kick you out?
She is winterizing the cottage.
which I just found out
does not mean decorating for Christmas.
Hey. cool lamp. What?
- What the hell?
- Thank you.
Ramona said
there's a thrift store in town.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Need a ride?
- Can I…
- No problem. I got you.
- Thank you so much.
Oh. actually. sorry.
I'm not taking this to the thrift.
It's my mom's. so I'm not able
to physically throw it out.
But I also can't bring it back
to the cottage
because Ramona asked me
to get rid of it all. so.
I wanted to ask you if it's okay if I...
and feel free to say no.
an annoying question...
if I can leave it with you
- for a little bit?
- Of course. Yeah.
Wait. so if you're keeping this stuff.
then why are we going to the thrift store?
Mmm. This should work. Right?
Yeah. I mean.
put that thing in the Louvre.
How do we charge this?
I think we plug it into the wall
or something?
- Or maybe batteries?
- Remember batteries?
Oh. my God. Remember batteries.
Okay. You didn't tell me Muskoka
is the fashion capital of the world.
- You didn't know that?
- These are so cool.
- Are they?
- Very.
Yeah. Go on.
Wow.
- What?
- I'm not even fucking with you when I say
that you look incredible in these.
- Oh. my… No. What? Never.
- Yes.
- No?
- Nope. not for me.
- Yes.
- I'm going to pass.
You have to get them.
- If you don't buy them. I will.
- What?
Peacock blue Huber Scoop chair.
This would be. like. $5.000 in New York.
- Jesus.
- Yeah. I know.
Wow.
Ha. ha.
Yeah. Mint condition.
- We're getting this.
- Shouldn't you be getting
rid of stuff and not bringing
more stuff back?
Technically. yes.
but this is perfect for Ramona.
She's redoing the cottage.
Maybe we could have.
like. a thing for her?
Yeah. Ramona hates things with people.
Right.
But it wouldn't have to be a thing-thing.
It could be like a small…
An intimate gathering. A casual hang.
Like. if we invited Sully. Oona.
just. like. a couple of her friends.
I just wanna. like. do something nice
for her. you know?
I… I admire your confidence.
How do you get chairs to islands?
- Are you sure...
- Yeah.
- I'm really happy to help. Okay.
- I got it.
- Shit! Shit!
- Whoa! Oh. fuck!
- Okay. I'm helping you. I'm sorry.
- Go left.
- Okay.
- Can I help?
- Hey.
- Sorry. can I...
- Wait. We're good. We're good.
- I got you.
- Back up. bro.
- Okay. Yeah. man.
- That's what I'm trying to do. Yeah.
- Just back it up. Nice.
- Okay. Careful. careful. careful.
- All right.
- Okay.
- That ain't so bad.
Good work.
- Thanks.
- Uh…
- Thank you. guys.
- So. fill me in.
What happened last night?
Who is that? Is that your sister?
- That...
- Did she kill you?
You know what? That is Ramona.
She is my sister.
and I got her this chair
for not killing me.
- Hell. yeah.
- And I'm alive.
Yes. good. I'm sure you're good
as long as this guy's around.
Man. I wish I could be there
when she sees her brand-new Huber Scoop.
- I...
- What?
We're doin' a thing
for Ramona tomorrow.
Really? I love things.
Can I… Can I come?
- You should come.
- Just a thing? Things are perfect.
- A small. chill thing.
- Things are my favorite.
- You're a thing guy.
- I am. kind of.
- Things are your thing. Cool.
- Yeah. Things are my thing.
All right. we should get going.
- Okay. cool.
- For sure.
Okay. Then I'll…
Yeah. I'll see you tomorrow.
- See you tomorrow.
- Perfect. See you too. man.
Are those… What are those. Chrome Hearts?
They look great on you. man.
Have a good one!
See? I told you they're cool.
What?
- Yo.
- Hey. So. already put an order in for you.
- You don't even know what I want.
- I know what you need.
- These are really good choices.
- Good taste. Can I sit?
Yeah. Cool.
Ugh. So.
how are things going
with Little Orphan Annie?
- I'm the orphan. remember?
- Shit. Sorry. Sorry.
Everything's fine. It's…
It's fine. Yeah.
- It's fine!
- Okay. so three "fines" is suspicious.
She's a lot. dude. It's like…
She won't stop asking all these questions.
Don't you have questions for her?
I mean. she lived with your mom
for longer than you did.
and she had a whole other life
and family in New York.
- I just met my wife.
- Oh.
Like. swear down.
- Right.
- Yeah.
Do you mean her? That girl over there?
The one who's quite literally
on a date right now?
Yeah. yeah.
She is on a date. but he just asked her
what her favorite color of car is.
- Color of car.
- That's so ridiculous.
- Yes. So. I think I'm in.
- Mmm. yeah.
- I feel like I'm in.
- Hell. yeah.
- Yeah.
Um. and I told her
that her food was free. so…
Oona. Do you…
Hey.
- Ugh. What is that?
- Uh. it's a…
new chair.
It's. uh… It's loud.
Um. it's hygge.
- It's Danish.
- For "fucking hideous"?
Yeah. yeah. Um.
I thought it'd be cute for you.
Since you said
you don't like the old furniture.
But. like. you totally
do not have to keep it.
It's. like. a lot.
Crazy color. so I should've…
Yeah.
It's semi-comfortable.
Okay.
Cool.
What's that noise?
Oh. has music
not made its way to Canada yet?
Funny.
- What is that? We don't need more shit.
- A small purchase...
I know you're sick of that song
'cause I've played it
1.000 times this summer.
but I had to put it on here because
I want you to know
I think about you every time I hear it.
On the docks. in the rain.
I never thought we'd kiss in the rain.
- So cliché.
- Who's that?
Goldie. wanna help me
clean up down here?
Dad. I'm recording!
Where'd you find that?
In the box you gave me and I know
I wasn't supposed to take anything.
I'm sorry about that. but this is
Mom's voice. right? And Gordon?
What year did that song come out?
The early '90s?
Because she must've recorded this
when she was our age.
- Ramona. I'm…
- Do not follow me.
Shit.
Anyway.
as much as I love that song.
it is nothing compared
to how much I love you. Joe.
Joe?
Ramona. whoa.
What happened?
Why are you soaking wet?
Did you swim here?
Kind of.
Do you wanna talk about it? No?
- No.
- Okay. let's get you out of these clothes.
- Hi.
- Hi. Joe.
- Annie. right?
- Mmm-hmm.
Ellis is still out on a job.
but he should be back soon.
No worries. I'm actually. um…
I'm here to see you.
So my mom was here. like.
every summer or was it year-round?
- Every summer.
- Okay.
Okay.
So you knew her pretty well. then?
Well. it is a small island.
so. yeah. we did okay.
I don't know if you remember.
and maybe it's weird.
but I found a tape that she made.
like a cassette mixtape thing. and I…
It feels like it was for you.
I don't remember that.
I mean. she could've.
Yeah. I mean.
it was a long time ago.
Yeah. she sounds really.
really young on it. but…
She's. like. talk… I actually have it.
She's talking to you.
and. I don't know.
it sounds like. from the tape.
that you guys were…
dating?
I mean. yeah. I…
We did. We…
We dated a couple of months
in high school.
That's all.
We were actually younger
than you guys. even.
Really?
Oh. that's… That's amazing.
Yeah. Just kids.
Okay. Did she always
wanna move to New York?
I mean. honestly. I can't tell you
that much about that part of her life.
Um. she obviously went to New York City.
she met your dad.
I stayed here. I met Kate. and…
I don't know. we… We lost touch.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
So obviously. I know
that she really loved this place.
So I was wondering if there's anything
you could tell me about.
like. what she liked to do here.
Yeah. there were things
she loved to do here.
She loved to cliff jump.
and she was a badass at it.
She loved to get up very early
in the morning
and canoe around the lake
before anyone was awake.
I remember her laying
underneath the trees. on the grass…
staring up and naming.
She named the trees?
Every single one of 'em.
That's really sweet.
- Yo.
- Dude.
Hey. I. like I said. got a repair to do
before dinner with this kid.
Do you mind if I borrow that?
Yeah. of course.
Go for it.
Thank you.
It was good talking to ya.
I will see you in a minute.
Yeah.
What's… What's goin' on?
You did not tell me that he and my mom
dated in high school.
Um. maybe 'cause I didn't know?
Oh. fuck. Was that. like. a secret?
I mean. yeah. clearly. from me.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to…
But you're coming tomorrow. right?
- Yeah. Yeah. yeah.
- Cool.
You're gonna need someone
to protect you from Ramona
since you're throwin' her a party.
- I am not throwing a party.
- Kinda. Kinda.
- It's not a party.
- Okay.
Maybe bring a small weapon.
- Will do.
- Okay.
See you later.
- See you.
- Bye.
I don't know. I feel like your mom left
that tape as a gift for you guys to find.
Was the pile of old socks I found
also a gift from the afterlife?
I know that you don't believe
in. like. this kind of stuff.
but honestly. sometimes I feel
like the universe is just smacking you
over your dumb. pretty head with signs.
and everyone else can see them except you.
Like. everyone else.
I can see the secret sister.
She won't leave me alone.
Yeah.
There might be something special
that comes out of that too.
Mmm.
Yeah. maybe.
I'm really glad that you came over.
I've missed having alone time with you.
Yeah.
- Yeah. me too.
- You feeling better?
Yeah.
Good.
- Okay.
Okay. Good night.
- Good night.
- I love you.
Hey.
Hi. Are you okay?
I was so worried
when you didn't come home last night...
Hey. we do not have
that kind of relationship.
- Why don't you sit down?
- Okay.
I wanted to say again
I'm sorry about yesterday.
I didn't know what was on the tape.
- and I never would've played it if I...
- Hey.
We're good. I just…
I don't know. I was just. like…
It was just hard hearing Gordon's voice.
Yeah. same.
Sure you get it.
being here with all of mom's stuff.
Um… Yeah. but honestly. like…
Like. I don't really remember anything.
Really?
Nothing?
I mean. like. one thing. but it's. like…
Like. I don't really know
if it's. like. an actual memory
or a picture or a story somebody told me.
so it's sort of probably not real.
Well. what is it?
- If you want to.
- No. yeah. Yeah. I don't care.
Um. it's like a…
I've never said it out loud.
It's like… We were. like. laying in bed.
and she's scratching my back...
like. scratchies. you know?
Um. and I can feel her breathing.
and it's like…
Like. I felt so. um. like.
like. warm and safe
and held and stuff. so…
Um… But. yeah.
I don't really know if it's real. so…
Sorry.
Where did you sleep?
Uh. Oona's.
Oh.
I feel like you wanna say
something inappropriate and invasive.
Me?
No.
Never. No. No.
I don't know. Do you guys have
a vibe or something? 'Cause...
Are you just assuming I'm gay?
No.
- I'm gay.
- Okay. okay.
Uh. you scared me there. Um…
Well. if you ever wanted to. like…
I'm here if you ever wanna discuss that.
elaborate on any of that. No. seriously.
Right. well. there's nothing
to elaborate on because…
I am not her type. so…
Then what's Oona's type?
Straight.
uh. unavailable. hot. perfect. pretty.
Like. everything I'm not.
I'm sorry.
How can you say that you're not pretty
when you look so much like Mom?
I don't look anything like her.
Ramona. you're her twin.
I'm. like. actually very jealous.
You're her DNA. Like…
I've wanted to hug you since I got here.
Is there any way I can hug you?
Absolutely not. No.
- Can I touch your arm?
- No.
Totally. Fair. Fair. fair. fair. fair.
Oh.
Hello?
Oliver. hey.
Thank you for pickin' up.
Mr. Jacobson.
Hi. Hi.
Um. what can I do for you. sir?
Can you put Annie on the phone?
Uh… No.
Yes. Yes. I can put Annie on the phone.
but she is in the bathroom.
She's not there with you?
I guess it depends.
Um. it depends what you mean
by "with me." right?
Like. do you mean it in a physical sense?
- Oliver. this is serious!
- 'Cause...
Where is Annie physically right now?
I have no idea where she is.
I'm not even lying. I have no idea.
- I'm sorry. Mr. Jacobson.
- Okay.
- Call me if you hear from her?
- Love you.
- What?
I will put the Soho House
on the west side.
I'll erect the first Canadian Erewhon
on the southeast...
Hey. where's your sister?
In my thoughts and prayers?
Right. okay. I know you lied.
I know she's not in Thailand.
I think we both have a pretty good idea
where she actually is.
I can literally see you
coming up with a lie right now.
Okay.
If you think she might have fled
to Canada. you might be not high.
I'm not fuckin' around.
You didn't tell us Mom was fully Canadian.
or that Grandpa was actually a fucking G
who left us an island.
or that we have a secret sister.
when I'm already at capacity with one.
Wait. what? What did you just say?
You said… Annie said secret sister?
- No.
- Connor!
Maybe.
Okay.
Okay. here we go. I am going up there.
- I'll book a flight right now.
- Dude. no. Do not do that.
- She's really mad at you.
- I know. That's why I gotta go up there.
- She won't answer my calls.
- But if you go there.
she's just gonna run somewhere else.
I mean. she's always wanted
to go to Norway.
and Norway is. like. really shitty.
Terrible quality of life. lots of crime.
I mean...
It leaves in two and a half hours.
Okay. fine. I will get over my lifelong.
debilitating wolf phobia to go out there
and fix this for you and drag her
back home so you can explain it to her.
Why do you suddenly wanna go do this?
When's the last time
you offered to help out?
Because I don't wanna lose her. Dad.
I wanna bring her home safely.
I wanna put this whole Canada chapter
to bed for all of us.
And frankly. Canada's random as fuck.
Ellis?
Ellis. baby.
- What's up?
- Ellis. Quick question.
Do you have a gift for the thing
at Ramona's tonight?
- What?
- Awesome.
So. Rory is definitely
going to bring a Diptyque candle.
or an Aesop exfoliating soap.
which he'll pair with an orange wine.
- Which means that...
- Okay. Sully. I love you.
I feel like I'm having a stroke.
What is that?
Bottom line is.
you need to get Annie something.
Okay. I mean. if I have time…
Make time! Sorry. Whoa.
I'm just really excited. Um…
Make time for her.
- Yes.
- Get her something nice.
I'm gonna iron my jorts now for tonight
and find deodorant with aluminum in it.
- That's important too.
- Oh. okay.
Bye! Kisses. bisous!
- See ya.
- Au revoir.
- I'll see you later.
- See ya.
Hey. Ramona.
Whoa. hey. Where are you going? A wedding?
No. I wanted to surprise you.
By the… Just…
Rory and. like. maybe Ellis
might stop by for a sec.
Wait. Are you throwing a party
at my house?
To say thanks for letting me stay here.
All right. Weird.
Well. I hate surprises.
and I'm going to bed. so…
Hi.
- Hey.
- Hey. beautiful mamas.
- Hey. gorgeous.
- Okay.
-This is amazing
-Thank you.
Don't even judge me for this.
I literally just put it together.
- No. it's awesome.
- I'll put it over there.
- I need to cancel.
- What? No!
- We have such good vibes.
- I know.
- Please.
- Ramona's really upset...
- Knock. knock. Wow.
- Hey.
You look stunning.
- Thanks.
- I brought you these.
Oh. my... I love orange wine.
- Thank you so much.
- You're so welcome.
- Um. is...
- Hey-yo! What's up?
- Lincoln.
- Yo. What happened here?
I didn't know that you were coming.
- You poor-poor now. huh?
- Or you. or you.
- I love it.
- Who are you?
Yo. what the fuck
is this chair. bro?
Goddamn! The vibes are not vibing.
This wasn't supposed
to look like this.
If we could just keep it super quiet.
that'd be really good.
Jesus Christ.
The party don't start till you walk in.
- Ew. Hated that.
- You love me so much. though.
Are you seriously quoting Kesha
at my face right now?
You're welcome.
Come on. don't be boring. Come downstairs
and eat my expensive cheese before Lincoln
and his posse of merry men do.
- Who the fuck is Lincoln?
- I literally don't know.
Also. isn't it ridiculous that she's
throwing a party at my cottage? Like...
Yeah. yeah. it infuriates me too.
God forbid she tries
to make you smile. Ramona.
Yeah. thanks. Thanks for getting it.
Oona is coming.
- So?
- Yeah. yeah. yeah. yeah. So? So?
I'll see you down there.
I never said I was coming.
- Wait. That's Ramona?
- You know what?
No. do you know what's insane?
I can't tell if that's my mom or Ramona.
- Seriously?
- Isn't that nuts?
This is so nice. though.
You get to have. like…
- You can discover all this. Memories.
- Yeah. it is. You're right.
Oh. my God. Chet Baker biography.
I love him. I dressed up as him.
like. four Halloweens in a row.
- You're not gonna believe this. Same.
- What?
- Really?
- No. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I…
But I was. like. a chessboard
a couple of times.
- You know.
- You were a chessboard?
Mmm-hmm.
Nice. What?
Were your friends. like. the pieces?
Never once. No.
They were. like. normal stuff.
- Like bumblebees and witches.
- So. what? You were just the board?
- You just went around as a solo board?
- Okay. says Chet Baker.
- What?
- Why weren't you. like. Beethoven?
Isn't that your whole thing? Like. piano?
No one would've known I was Beethoven.
'cause you can't take a piano around.
Did you not bring your piano tonight?
- No.
- That's a shame.
You could have tickled the…
- You could have...
- What? You want me to tickle the ivories?
- No.
- That's what you were about to say.
Why would I? That'd be crazy.
I don't tickle anymore. anyway.
- What? Why?
- What?
- Why don't I tickle?
- Why don't you play? You were a prodigy.
I know. but when you're…
When you're a weird child prodigy
for classical piano.
it can sometimes bring with it. like.
way too much fame.
- Too much fortune.
- Yeah. Oh. God.
And it was taking its toll on my life
and my wife. Susan.
- Yes!
- And my kids.
Susan. Susan.
- Mmm-hmm.
- How is Susan?
- Susan left me.
- No!
- I know!
- No. it's all good.
- That's really hard.
I like being single.
Do you?
- Do I like being single?
- Yeah.
- Are you?
- Am I single?
Mmm-hmm.
Uh… Um…
- Should we unpack this over a drink?
- Yeah.
- Can I make you one?
- Nice.
- Thanks.
Okay. look after Chet.
Yeah.
You're joking.
Ramona. Hey.
- Hi.
- Okay. whoa. This is fun.
Yeah? I don't know if that's the word
I'd use to describe it. but...
Sorry. this is the beautiful
Stacey Mallory.
- Hi.
- She's a counselor at Camp Queen E.
Hey.
- You want a drink. babe?
- Yeah.
I'll see you in a bit?
- Hey. babe.
- Hi.
Hey.
I'm so sorry.
- Hey. dude. What's that?
- Hey.
Uh. nothing.
Fuck.
Seems like something.
I'm just…
- fixing this.
- For what?
For Annie.
Be careful.
Dad. I'm wearing gloves. Come on.
Yeah. I'm not talkin'
about the lamp. Ellis.
They always leave end of the summer.
Running is. like.
the only thing in my life that can really
keep up with me. you know?
It. like. keeps me sane.
Running is just walking for people
who don't have a personality.
I'm gonna go smoke.
Hey.
- Hey. Oona. Hi.
- Hi.
Hi. Uh…
Ramona was just looking for you.
Outside. I think.
- Okay. Okay. cool. Okay. see ya.
- Cool. See ya.
Mona.
- Hey.
- Oona. Hey.
Having fun?
Yeah. It's a good vibe in there.
Yeah. It's a good vibe.
Thank you.
Think Stacey Mallory's okay.
you leaving her alone for this long?
You know. her being sedentary.
not running.
Well. she's a trooper.
You know. she's soldiering through.
Do you… You think you like her?
I mean…
I like all of them.
Right.
Like. she's not just another
camp counselor
in a long. very hot line
of camp counselors.
I think she might be the one.
Oh.
I'm joking. babe.
No. She's not the one.
- Okay.
- No. it's just. like. a casual hookup.
Why?
- No reason.
- Why? Are you jealous?
Oh.
Oona!
Um…
Oona. get back here!
- Yeah.
- I should probably go.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go.
Yeah. yeah.
- Oona!
- Yep. I'm here.
- Outside?
- It's where it is.
We're goin' outside?
Well. this is the porch.
- Nice.
- Welcome to the porch.
- Thanks for having me.
- You're welcome.
And these are some lights
that I cannot believe Ramona let us hang.
- That's cool.
- Yeah.
She's usually not super
into that kinda thing.
And this is the outside. which is…
- Dark.
- Dark and spooky.
Yeah.
Well. at least you got the lights.
Yeah. Although it's kinda scary
with the wood. huh?
What?
'Cause it's just. like.
an electrical hazard.
Potential fire hazard.
So it's all scaring me.
Um. the…
I'm scared of fire haz…
I'm careful about fire hazards.
and so I found a book here
that says you need a circuit interrupter
to prevent one with these lights
depending on where the wood's from.
- So. I'm...
- Annie.
I'm gonna kiss you.
Yeah.
Hi.
You here to apologize
for being an asshole?
Okay. Good night.
No. I'm kidding. Annie.
Sorry.
It's okay. I'm sorry too.
I saw you kissing Timmy Chalamet.
No. He kissed me.
And then I kissed him back.
How was it?
Um…
It was…
It was good.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah. it was. like…
like. really good.
Wow.
Little shocked you like him.
- But. hey. love is love.
- No. I don't…
Okay. I don't. like. like him.
I don't really think I…
I don't think I've ever really liked
anyone like that. I don't think.
I don't know. I don't know.
Something really weird happened with Oona.
Tell me everything right now.
I don't even…
I really don't know if I can explain it.
Try.
It was like…
Our faces were. like.
so close to each other.
- Like. I could feel her breathing on me.
- Okay. Hot.
And then she touched my thigh.
- Ah! Okay. So she's in love with you.
- She's not. No.
'Cause that was it.
- Nothing else happened.
- Really?
And it's so confusing
'cause I can't figure her out.
I can't tell what she's thinking.
And it's driving me insane.
but I'm like.
"Why touch my thigh like that?"
- You know? Like...
- No. 100%. 100%. actually.
Ugh! How did you guys leave it?
Well. she left with Stacey Mallory. so…
- Fuck. Ramona. I'm so sorry. That sucks.
- No. it's fine.
- No. that's… That sucks.
- Yeah. I know. It's fine. though.
It's fine.
Um…
guess I should go to sleep.
Yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Good night.
Sorry. do you… Wait.
Do you wanna…
Do you wanna sleep in here tonight?
- Seriously?
- Well. you don't snore. do you?
No. no. Um…
Although I have been told
I occasionally monologue in my sleep.
Oh. that's kinda scary.
- Please. still. can I? Please?
- Of course you do.
It's not that bad.
- That makes so much sense.
- Oh. my God.
- Ah!
- Jesus! Fuck.
Hi. I want in on the long-lost
sister-bonding. It's so cute.
Oh. I'm Connor. by the way.
And. guys. someone left
this adorable dog lamp out front. And…
Can I have it? I need it.
but not for. like. a night light.
- I'll explain later.
- What the fuck are you doing here?
So. I zillowed the place. and the cottage
is obviously a piece of shit.
- but the island itself is worth…
- Okay.
…$22.7 million. and since we all own it.
split three ways...
I'm sorry. What the fuck did you just say?
Split three ways?
- Oh. Annie didn't tell you.
- Told me what?
Tell you nothing because
we are not selling this island. Connor.
Grandpappy left the island to us too.
So now it's a threesome. guys.
Let's fuckin' sell this bitch.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org